let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who has the highest number of stumpings?",
    answer: "MS Dhoni",
    options: [
      "Kumar Sangakkara",
      "Quinton De Kock",
      "MS Dhoni",
      "Adam Gilchrist"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which team has the most IPL trophies?",
    answer: "Mumbai Indians",
    options: [
      "Mumbai Indians",
      "Chennai Super Kings",
      "Gujrat Titans",
      "Royal Challengers Bangalore"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who bowled the fastest delivery in cricket history?",
    answer: "Shoaib Akhtar",
    options: [
      "Chamika Karunaratne",
      "Shoaib Akhtar",
      "Lasith Malinga",
      "Jasprit Bumrah"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "When was the first World Cup held?",
    answer: "1975",
    options: [
      "2000",
      "1970",
      "1965",
      "1975"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who is the only player to hit a six in the first ball of a test innings?",
    answer: "Chris Gayle",
    options: [
      "Chris Gayle",
      "TM Dilshan",
      "Rohit Sharma",
      "Steve Smith"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who is known as 'Captain Cool'?",
    answer: "MS Dhoni",
    options: [
      "Kumar Sangakkara",
      "MS Dhoni",
      "Kane Williamson",
      "Shahid Afridi"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who has taken the highest number of wickets?",
    answer: "Muttiah Muralitharan",
    options: [
      "Jofra Archer",
      "Shane Warne",
      "Mitchell Starc",
      "Muttiah Muralitharan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who is known as the king of cricket?",
    answer: "Virat Kohli",
    options: [
      "Virat Kohli",
      "Kumar Sangakkara",
      "Sachin Tendulkar",
      "Chris Gayle"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is known as Mr.360?",
    answer: "AB de Villiers",
    options: [
      "Suryakumar Yadav",
      "TM Dilshan",
      "AB de Villiers",
      "David Warner"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who has scored the highest runs in one innings?",
    answer: "Brian Lara",
    options: [
      "Rohit Sharma",
      "Chris Gayle",
      "Sanath Jayasuriya",
      "Brian Lara"
    ]
  }
];